

CONTACT ME AT

1-345-927-3663

georgewauchope10@gmail.com

www.georgewauchope.com



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/g eorge-wauchope/

SKILLS SUMMARY

HTML

Javascript

React JS

Firebase

WordPress

Fast learner

GEORGE WAUCHOPE

FRONT-END SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I'm a front-end focused software developer, with experience in HTML, CSS, Javascript & React JS. I also have some backend experience with Node JS, Express & Firebase.

I am 24 years old & hold Caymanian (Cayman Islands), British & German citizenships. I speak English & Spanish. I'm also a blue belt in jiujitsu.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Co-founder at Giftgoat

May 2020 to January 2021

- I did the UI & UX for the entire website, and led a team of developers to build this project.
- https://www.giftgoat.com/

Director at Jexan Cayman

November 2018 to December 2020

- I was in charge of SEO for multiple client websites.
- https://www.jexan.com/

Founder of George's Watersports and Thingstodocayman.net

September 2014 to Present

- I built a watersports company and website in Grand Cayman.
- Within 5 years, thingstodocayman.net was doing sixfigures per month in revenue (pre-Covid).

EDUCATION

University of London

BSc, Computer Science (Web & Mobile Development) - 2021